A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Records and Institutional Support, 1985-1995; 2
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Declinations) - Sergeyev, Boris, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 953)
  - Workshop in Post-Soviet Sociology and Anthropology (Declinations) - Volkov, Vadim, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 954)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics - Hendley, Kathryn, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 955)
    File consists of a letter of recommendation for Hendley from Gail Lapidus. There are no other documents in the file.
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Amsden, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 956)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Ballard, Elza, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 957)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Buckley, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 958)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Carter, Stephen, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 959)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Clark, Terry D., 1989 (Box 78, Folder 960)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Dale, John Patrick, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 961)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Daley, Tad (Claude, III), 1989 (Box 79, Folder 962)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Derleth, James, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 963)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Frost, Howard, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 964)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Harvey, Brian, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 965)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Heywood, Anthony, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 966)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Plumb-Jamison, Dawn E., 1989 (Box 79, Folder 967)
    Empty folder. File contained only a transcript page, which was not retained.
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Poptsova-Cook, Elena, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 968)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Shlapentokh, Dmitry, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 969)
  - Workshop on Soviet Domestic Politics (Declinations) - Yarsike, Debbie, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 970)
    File consists of application cover sheet only.
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Clem, James (Withdrew), 1993 (Box 79, Folder 971)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Crowley, Stephen (Withdrew), 1993 (Box 79, Folder 972)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Dakin, Mary, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 973)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Easter. Gerald, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 974)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Foglesong, Todd, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 975)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Frye, Timothy, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 976)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Gorlizki, Yoram, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 977)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Gurenko, Eugene (Withdrew), 1993 (Box 79, Folder 978)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Harris, James, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 979)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Herman, Robert, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 980)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Holiman, Alan, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 981)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Jamison, Dawn Plumb, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 982)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Kharkhordin, Oleg, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 983)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - King, Charles, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 984)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Kuenzi, David (Withdrew), 1993 (Box 79, Folder 985)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Merritt, Martha, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 986)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Moser, Robert, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 987)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Ostrow, Joel, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 988)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Robertson, Lawrence, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 989)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Rodkey, Gretchen, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 990)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Thorson, Carla, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 991)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Woodruff, David, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 992)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Young, John, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 993)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Barrington, Lowell, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 994)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Bremmer, Ian, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 995)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Burns, Katherine, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 996)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Chase, Judith, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 997)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Davis, Susan, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 998)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Gottlick, Jane, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 999)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Hamilton, Anne, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1000)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Luong, Pauline Jones, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1001)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Omarova, Saule, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1002)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Rotnam, Thomas, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1003)
    The two reference forms each refer to attached letters, but these letters are not in the file.
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Weinthal, Erika, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1004)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Bleiere, Daina (Latvia) (Withdrew), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1005)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Karimova, Zulfia (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1006)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Kharitonova, Oksana (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1007)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Klynchenko, Oleh (Ukraine), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1008)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Makeshin, Alexei (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1009)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Milyukova, Irina (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1010)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Ruban, Larisa (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1011)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Terk, Eric (Estonia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1012)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Tolipov, Farhad (Uzbekistan), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1013)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Zaznaev, Oleg (Russia), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1014)
  - Workshop on Post-Soviet Domestic Politics - Kirsanova, Ludmilla (Russia) (Alternate), 1994 (Box 80, Folder 1015)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (I) - Barrett, Thomas, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1016)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (I) - Jersild, Austin, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1017)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (I) - Katsev, Allison, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1018)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (I) - Smith, Douglas, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1019)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (I) - Thumim, Donald, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1020)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (II) - Farrow, Lee, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1021)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (II) - Knight, Nathaniel, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1022)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (II) - Schimmelpenninck van der Oye, David, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1023)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (II) - Sunderland, Willard, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1024)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (II) - Thomas, Kevin, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1025)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (Declinations) - Brown, Stephen, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1026)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (Declinations) - Burbee, Carolynn, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1027)
  - Workshop on Imperial Russian History (Declinations) - Burwood, Linnea, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1028)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants (General), 1993-1994 (Box 81, Folder 1029)
    Funding history and award letters. Grant program for Faculty Professional Development and Retraining in the Study of the Former Soviet Union.
  - Postdoctoral (Faculty) Retraining Grants - Cutler, Robert, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1030)
  - Postdoctoral (Faculty) Retraining Grants - Schubel, Vernon James, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1031)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Brubaker, Rogers, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1031)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Christoffersen, Gaye, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1033)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Cook, Linda, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1034)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Gleason, William, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1035)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Hanks, Reuel (Award Declined), 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1036)
    Hanks declined the award as he had also been selected to participate in a NEH workshop that sumer.
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Kangas, Roger, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1037)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants - Schubel, Vernon, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1038)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants (Declinations) - Bogomazola, Tatyana, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1039)
  - Faculty Retraining Grants (Declinations) - Clifford, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1040)
  - Faculty Retraining Grant (Declinations) - House, Richard, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1041)
  - Faculty Retraining Grant (Declinations) - Webel, Charles, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1042)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Chase, William, 1991 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1908)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Zimmerman, William, 1991 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1909)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Buckley, Cynthia, 1991 Fall (Box 120, Folder 1910)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Deych, Genrich, 1991 Fall (Box 120, Folder 1911)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Burawoy, Michael, 1992 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1912)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Checkel, Jeffrey, 1992 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1913)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Kerig, Patricia, 1992 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1914)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Martin, Russell, 1992 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1915)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Gasparov, Boris, 1992 Fall (Box 120, Folder 1916)
  - JCSS - Research and Development Program - Johnson, Robert E., 1992 Fall (Box 120, Folder 1917)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Stevens, Carol, 1993 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1918)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Kiaer, Christina, 1993 Fall (Box 120, Folder 1919)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Balzer, Marjorie, 1994 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1920)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Ryan-Hayes, Karen, 1994 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1921)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Yates, Steven, 1994 Spring (Box 120, Folder 1922)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Noonan, Thomas, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1923)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Rabinowitz, Stanley, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1924)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Rozman, Gilbert, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1925)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Stoner-Weiss, Kathryn, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1926)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program - Owen, Thomas, 1995 Fall (Box 121, Folder 1927)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Brudny, Yitzhak and Peter Rutland, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1043)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Hellie, Richard, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1044)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Keith, Patricia, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1045)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Shalin, Dmitri, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1046)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Sullivan, Stefan, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1047)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Szporluk, Roman, 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1048)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Uzzell, Lawrence (Jamestown Foundation), 1991 Spring (Box 81, Folder 1049)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Brovkin, Vladimir, 1991 Fall (Box 81, Folder 1050)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1051)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Hunter, Holland, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1052)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kerig, Patricia, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1053)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Morris, Richard, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1054)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Rosefielde, Steven, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1055)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Shalin, Dmitri, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1056)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Stanley, Rebecca, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1057)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Super-Optimum Solutions Group, 1991 Fall (Box 82, Folder 1058)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Abt, Clark, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1059)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Basok, Tanya, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1060)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Benifand, Alexander, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1061)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Bonnell, Victoria, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1062)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Castellano, Charlene, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1063)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Cook, Linda, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1064)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Coopersmith, Jonathan, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1065)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Daly, Gerald, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1066)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Dean, Bridget, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1067)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Freinkman, Lev, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1068)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Galin, Igor, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1069)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - International School of Ukrainian Studies (Kiev), 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1070)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Johnson, Mark, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1071)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Karpat, Kemal, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1072)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Koester, David, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1073)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kornblatt, Judith, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1074)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Krieger, Joel, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1075)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Latin American - Caribbean Center, Florida International University, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1076)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Linden, Ronald, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1077)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Melmon, Kenneth, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1078)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Murav, Harriet, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1079)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Neumaier, Diane, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1080)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Nichols, James, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1081)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Northern Illinois University, Center for Governmental Studies, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1082)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - O'Brien, David, 1992 Spring (Box 82, Folder 1083)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Rosefielde, Steven, 1992 Spring (Box 83, Folder 1084)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Shalin, Dmitri, 1992 Spring (Box 83, Folder 1085)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Todd, W. Russell, 1992 Spring (Box 83, Folder 1086)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Zettner, Steven, 1992 Spring (Box 83, Folder 1087)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Barr, Donald, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1088)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Claster, Jill, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1089)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Demko, George, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1090)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Fine, John, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1091)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Holmes, Stephen, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1092)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Ilyashov, Anatoli, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1093)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kincade, William, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1094)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Koester, David, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1095)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kornblatt, Judith Deutsch, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1096)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kotkin, Stephen, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1097)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Launer, Michael, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1098)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Leonard, Carol, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1099)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Linden, Ronald, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1100)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Magocsi, Paul, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1101)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Marshev, Vadim, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1102)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Mauro, Frank, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1103)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Moltz, James Clay, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1104)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - O'Hara, C. Joseph, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1105)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Poe, Marshall, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1106)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Rayport, Jennifer, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1107)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Rutland, Peter, 1992 Fall (Box 83, Folder 1108)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Schillinger, Elisabeth, 1992 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1109)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Slavinska, Nonna, 1992 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1110)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Urban, Michael, 1992 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1111)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Wasserkrug, Sue, 1992 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1112)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Waters, Michael, 1992 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1113)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Brubaker, Rogers, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1114)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Clark, Carol, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1115)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Engel, Barbara, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1116)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Glad, Peter, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1117)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Glicksman, Allen and Tanya Koropeckyj-Cox, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1118)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Higgins, Ann, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1119)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Huttenbach, Henry, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1120)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Johnson, Mark, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1121)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kazanjian, Miriam, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1122)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kovalev, Andrei, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1123)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Leonard, Carol, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1124)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - McCutcheon, Robert, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1125)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Onyshkevych, Larissa, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1126)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Sacks, Michael, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1127)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Tritten, James, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1128)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Von Hagen, Mark and Alexander Motyl, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1129)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Walker, Philip, 1993 Spring (Box 84, Folder 1130)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Bagley, Carole, 1993 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1131)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - David-Fox, Michael, 1993 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1132)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Johnson, Mark, 1993 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1133)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kaufman, Stuart, 1993 Fall (Box 84, Folder 1134)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Leonard, Carol, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1135)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Onyshkevych, Larissa, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1136)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Reisinger, William, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1137)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Silverman, Melvin, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1138)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Solomon, Peter, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1139)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Sprinkle, Robert, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1140)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Urban, Joan, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1141)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Yates, Steven, 1993 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1142)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Buck-Morss, Susan, 1994 Spring (Box 85, Folder 1143)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Castells, Manuel, 1994 Spring (Box 85, Folder 1144)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Leaver, Betty Lou, 1994 Spring (Box 85, Folder 1145)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Metcalf, Lee, 1994 Spring (Box 85, Folder 1146)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Saivetz, Carol, 1994 Spring (Box 85, Folder 1147)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1148)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Hochhauser, Gail, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1149)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Holzman, Lois, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1150)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kanet, Roger, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1151)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kaufman, Stuart, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1152)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Koester, David, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1153)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Kullberg, Judith, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1154)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Moore, John, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1155)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Petersen, Phillip, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1156)
  - Research and Development (Declinations) - Schecter, Joel, 1994 Fall (Box 85, Folder 1157)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Davidheiser, Evelyn, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1928)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Deci, Edward, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1929)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Jose, Paul, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1930)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Kangas, Roger, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1931)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Leaver, Betty Lou, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1932)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Legvold, Robert, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1933)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Maslach, Christina, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1934)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Miller, Arthur, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1935)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Onyshkevych, Larissa, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1936)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Perlman, Bruce, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1937)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Petrov, Alexander, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1938)
  - JCSSS - Research and Development Program (Declinations) - Radon, Jenik, 1995 Spring (Box 121, Folder 1939)